[theme music playing]
[Arthur] There's no place
for justice in Ardiente!
What do we have?
Violence, bloodshed, and wealth!
And that's what I'm going
to take from you!
Ivy isn't here! She's not here!
Put Ivy Aguas on the phone.
[muffled] Hon! Hon!
[Arthur] Think twice about
everything you're going to do.
You don't want to marry
a corpse, now do you?
[Jepoy] I know you met
with Julio Ardiente.
What did you two talk about?
Will you sell Jaguar out?
-[Rufo] Will you rat me out?
-[Jepoy] Why not?
[Rufo] Well, I guess I have no choice.
Help!
Jaguar! I saw him talking
to Julio Ardiente.
[man] The boss is asking
what reward you want.
Money or weapons?
I want to be part of your group.
[Arnaldo] Ivy? Ivy.
-[muffled screaming]
-Ivy?
[Ivy crying] Why did he kidnap me?
[Arnaldo] Forgive me.
This is all my fault.
[grunts]
So, your informant's not responding, huh?
Maybe Jaguar has already intercepted him.
I want you to mount a manhunt
against this hoodlum Jaguar.
I want you to find him,
catch him, and kill him.
[Raul] Welcome to my group.
From now on, that will be your uniform.
There's one thing I ask of you.
I just want you to be loyal to me.
Then you'll get everything you want.
[Jepoy] Loud and clear, boss.
[Arnaldo] We want our wedding
to happen soon.
-How soon?
-Next week.
We can make that happen. And don't worry.
I will make sure nothing will
get in the way of your wedding.
Diego, I'll leave it up to you
to explain to Mom.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Don't let anyone find out
about what happened to me.
Okay, Ivy.
Thank you for understanding, Diego.
I'll call you again later.
Ivy, please take care.
Diego?
Was that Lily?
Uh… Yes, Auntie.
She says not to worry. She's doing okay.
That's great news.
All right, we'll be off, okay?
Okay. Take care.
Let's go.
Anna.
Jepoy.
Don't bother coming back
until you have Arthur's body.
I'll pay you whatever you want
as long as you kill that bastard.
Understood, Mayor.
[sinister music playing]
Grandpa.
How long have you been there?
-Uh… I was talking--
-Arnaldo…
There's no need for you
to stutter or cover this up.
[scoffs]
Because I already know
what happened to Miss Aguas.
Now,
what I want to know
is who was behind this.
Do you think…
it's Diego?
[tense music playing]
That bastard.
[Arnaldo breathing sharply]
Follow him.
[Fernan] That was delicious, Loring.
-Thank you so much.
-[Pandoy chuckles]
-[Loring] No problem.
-[Pandoy] You know you're always
-welcome here.
-[Loring] That's right.
Hey, go straight home, okay?
-Don't go wandering off, okay?
-They're…
-What?
-They're asking us…
-[Arnaldo] Diego!
-[Loring] Oh!
-…to come drink with them.
-[Loring] Hold on.
-It's the mayor.
-[Arnaldo] Diego!
[ominous music playing]
[Loring] Oh.
-Where's Diego?
-[Loring] Um…
-What brings you here, Mayor?
-[Arnaldo] Where's Diego?!
Diego!
-[Loring] Uh…
-Get out of there!
-Mayor. Mayor.
-Looks like…
You had too much to drink, Mayor.
-Diego!
-[Fernan] Calm down, Mayor.
[Pandoy] Good evening, Mayor.
-Mayor…
-[Arnaldo] Bring me Diego.
-[Pandoy] Mayor…
-Arnaldo!
You think I don't know what you did?
What are you doing here?
You had Arthur kidnap Ivy.
-What are you talking about?
-I know all your plans.
You did that so I'd lose
my focus on the campaign.
[scoffs]
All this time! How could I be so stupid?!
During the debate… In the restaurant…
You were behind everything.
-Well, now, I'm here.
-[Marlon] Mayor.
-Why?! What?!
-[Diego] Batch! Batch! Batch!
All of you! You're all to blame!
All of you. Everything that's happening…
Why didn't I think of this before?!
It's you!
You did all that!
-Go home.
-[Arnaldo laughs in disbelief]
-Just go home.
-Yes, I will go home
because I have a life to destroy.
But before that,
I want everyone to know that
I'm aware of what you're doing.
Especially you.
You can't stop our wedding.
Don't forget that. And not you!
Not you! Not you!
Not you can stop me from being
the governor of this town.
Not you.
It's me.
I'll put a stop to all your plans.
Bullshit!
[Arnaldo chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[car engine starts]
[music stops]
[tense music playing]
Jaguar.
[Emilia sighs]
I just don't want Papa, Arnaldo,
and Ivy Aguas keeping secrets from me.
I've been telling you.
You should choose me.
I won't keep secrets from you.
For whatever it's worth,
thank you so much for listening.
You have my undivided attention, Emilia.
I'm not like your husband.
He's not there when you need him most.
He won't listen to me anyway.
He'll just laugh at me.
That's how people are
when they aren't interested to listen.
They won't pay attention to you.
[Raul] Go ahead.
Tell me everything you want to say.
I'm here to listen.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Jaguar.
[sinister music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[pulls handbrake]
Who do you think is capable
of leading this town?
Aside from us, the Ardientes?
Who else? Tell us! Who?!
Me.
I will run for governor
against you, Arnaldo.
Ivy, be careful.
[sinister music playing]
[Arnaldo] You can't help
but be jealous of me, can you?
Ever since we were kids,
you've always wanted what I had.
Mom's love, Grandpa's love,
and Ivy.
Hon?
Arnaldo.
-[grunts]
-[Ivy] Arnaldo!
Arnaldo, enough!
If you don't believe me,
if you think I'm betraying you…
I guess, Arnaldo,
let's just stop this.
We should call off our wedding.
[tense music playing]
[sobs]
No!
No! Ivy's mine!
She's all mine!
She's mine!
She's mine, and she's mine alone.
No. No!
She's all mine.
She's mine alone.
Ivy's mine. Ivy's mine alone. Ivy's mine.
[exhales]
[sinister music playing]
But…
But who… [mumbling]
But who needs Ardiente?
Who needs Ardiente? Who needs power?
[exhales]
No. I don't need everything.
Ivy's all I need.
Just Ivy.
-[tense music playing]
-[whispering inaudibly]
Boss Jaguar says…
the Ardientes are hot on our trail.
He also heard that…
Julio Ardiente asked his friend
who has a private army
to hunt us down.
But we won't let them intimidate us.
We'll continue with our casino operations.
Then, you'll need me in those operations.
-[tense music playing]
-[whispering inaudibly]
Madrigal…
The boss says you'll be guarding
the house for now.
And if you'll defy his orders,
then you'll be sorry.
[whispering inaudibly]
One more thing, Madrigal.
The boss' only wish…
is for you to wear
the uniform he gave you.
[tense music playing]
Hon? Hon? Hon, hon, hon.
Get up. Get up. Get up.
-Wake up. Wake up. Get up.
-Hon?
-Let's go. Let's get out of here.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-Wait. Ouch! Ouch!
-Arnaldo!
-I'm… I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
-I'm sorry!
-What's going on?
No, no, no, no, no. This is--
No, no, no, no. We have to do this.
-What, hon?
-I have to do this.
I have to do this. We have to do this.
-Hon! What's happening?
-No, no, no.
-Hold on!
-Let's go. Let's go.
"Let's go" where? Where are we going? Why?
Let's leave Poblacion Ardiente.
-Huh?
-I'm begging you.
Let's leave everything behind.
Let's get away from my family.
Away from my family. Away from everyone
-who's trying to ruin us.
-Is my kidnapper here, hon?
-No, no, no, no, no!
-Is Arthur there?
-I won't let anything
-Hon, is he back?
-happen to you.
-What's happening?!
No, no, no, no, no!
-Is he there?!
-I won't…
I won't let anything happen to you.
-Is my kidnapper there?
-It's just that I…
No, no, no, no! I thought… I thought…
I thought of something.
-What?
-Let's get away from here.
-What's happening?
-Let's start a new life
somewhere else, okay?
Let's start a new life somewhere else.
Away from my family.
Away from Poblacion Ardiente.
Away from everyone who's trying to ruin--
Away from this mess!
Let's go to Hong Kong.
We will get married there.
Okay? I will marry you.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-I will…
I will marry you there, okay?
[stutters] Let's start
a new life somewhere.
Away. Away from this.
-Away from all of it.
-Hon.
Away from everything.
Away from everything. Please?
-Hon.
-Please?
-Please? Let's go.
-Hon, hold on.
No, no, no, no, no.
The chopper's waiting for us.
It's taking us to the airport.
We can go now. We can go now.
Yes, but hold on.
Hon, I can't just leave.
What about Aguas Realty, my business?
I can't just leave it. I… I'm sorry!
Your mother, your… your grandpa.
He just said yes.
He just agreed
that we'd get married next week.
Hon…
Hon, relax!
You scared me. I thought Arthur,
-my kidnapper, was back.
-No.
-Hon…
Okay. Do you need assurance?
Assurance? Is that it, hon?
I will get married to you
because I truly do love you.
If someone dares to stop our wedding,
I won't let them.
We'll get married
come hell or high water, hon.
Because I love you.
I'm all yours, hon.
That's why I'm getting married to you.
I will become
Mrs. Ivy Aguas-Ardiente-Torillo.
I promise you,
I will get married to you
because I love you.
Hon, I love you.
Hon, you frightened me.
I thought my kidnapper was back again.
-No. No.
-Look at me, look at me.
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo, I love you.
I… I… I love you.
-I love you so much.
-I'm gonna marry you.
[sniffles] I love you so much.
[mumbling]
We're getting married, right?
Yeah.
We're getting married.
-I love you.
-You're mine!
Yes, I'm yours.
-You're mine. Okay?
-And you're mine, right?
-You're mine.
[Ivy sniffles]
[whispers] Yes.
[tense music playing]
[inaudible]
[echoes] Well?!
[echoes] Ha!
-[grunting, screaming in pain]
-[laughing]
[tense music playing]
[Anna] Jepoy, come in.
Come in.
Anna, thanks again for helping me out.
You're welcome.
[Jepoy groans]
-Is it okay if I stay here?
-Of course.
Thank you.
It's just that it's been
a while since we last spoke.
And you suddenly texted me,
asking me to have you picked up.
Why? Did something happen in Ardiente?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Jepoy groans]
Jepoy, I'm not as innocent
as you and Lily think.
I know that you work
for Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente.
Did he do that to you?
[Jepoy exhales sharply]
-Jepoy…
-Anna…
Jepoy, whatever it is, you have
to tell me the whole truth.
[quietly] Anna, please.
Fine. You should get some rest, okay?
[tense music playing]
See you later.
[door closes]
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
-[music intensifies]
-[breathing heavily]
Jepoy?
Jepoy?!
Why do you have those wounds?!
What did they do to you?!
[uneasy music playing]
[quietly] Anna…
What happened to you, Jepoy?!
[water sloshing]
Tell me, Jepoy.
Did Lily go there
so she could exact her revenge?
Jepoy, tell me the truth.
Were the Ardientes behind
the murder of Lily's parents?
[in normal voice] Anna…
Lily went to Ardiente to seek revenge.
That's the truth.
You're going up against
very powerful people.
Just look at what they've done to you.
They almost killed you!
Anna, I'm ready to die for Lily!
I'm not done yet.
I'm just getting started.
[breathes heavily]
I'm going back to Ardiente
to finish them all off.
[breathing heavily]
Jepoy, I don't know what I can do to help,
but we should treat your wounds first.
[tense music playing]
[Jepoy groans]
[dramatic choral music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
[Jepoy] Now that I'm back,
I will make you suffer
much worse than I did back then.
I will take down
every member of your family!
I'll start with Arnaldo
so he can't get married to Ivy.
After that, you're next, Julio and Emilia.
I will use Jaguar's weapons
to wipe out the entire Ardiente clan!
[glass clinking]
Could I have your undivided attention?
I have a very, very important
announcement to make.
What is it, Papa?
[shushes] Emilia, just listen.
As you all know, it's been quite a while
that we have been preparing
for the forthcoming…
Aguas-Ardiente royal wedding.
And I'm very, very happy to inform you…
that it is finally going to happen…
a week from today.
-[Ivy chuckles]
-[Claire] Really?
Wow! Congratulations! Congratulations!
-[Julio] Yes.
-What?
What?!
No! No, no, no! [pounds on table]
No, Papa!
Emilia! What's wrong with you? What is it?
[tense music playing]
[Julio] What?
Can't you see the problem, Papa?!
A wedding in a week?!
You're all insane!
Especially you, Papa!
Me? [scoffs]
Yes! A wedding in a week?
How? How, Aunt Claire?
Can you please tell me, Papa?!
How?!
We don't even have a caterer!
I don't have a designer
for my gown yet, Papa.
What do I do? That's a big problem.
Emilia, you're worried
about your wedding gown?
I'm the one getting married, not you.
You act like this is your wedding.
We have money, we can find a way.
That's right, and we have
so many people at our disposal.
-[Julio] Mm-hmm.
-[Arnaldo] Okay?
They will work 24/7 if they have to
just for this wedding to push through.
Thanks, hon.
[tense music playing]
Okay, if that's the case,
then, go on with the wedding.
I support you.
[tense music playing]
-[sinister music playing]
-Once we reach the casino,
go straight to the cashiers.
Get everything you can get.
Don't shoot unless necessary.
I want this to be a clean job.
Remember this…
We're going outside Ardiente,
it isn't our turf.
Understood?
Yes, boss.
Let's go.
Boss? Maybe I can go with you?
I'm ready.
[whispering inaudibly]
Just taking my chances, boss.
I'm more useful out there than in here.
The boss wants to know
if you really want to do this.
Yes.
Have some faith, boss.
I swear I'll be your best
and most trusted man.
[whispering inaudibly]
[man 2] The boss agrees.
He says just make sure you don't screw up.
Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[music transitions to suspenseful]
[horn honking]
[music stops]
[tense music playing]
That's the group the boss
was talking about.
Congressman Ardiente
wants us to take them out.
What are we waiting for? Let's get them.
Okay. I'll call for backup.
You know what to do.
Take your positions inside.
Wait for my signal.
-Yes, boss.
[tense music playing]
[indistinct conversations]
Sir, we're positive it's them.
We need backup.
[tense music playing]
[gun clicks]
[gun cocks]
-[line ringing]
-Jaguar, pick up!
[clinking]
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
[suspenseful music building]
Boss!
They followed us. Julio Ardiente's men.
Boss, it isn't safe to do this now.
[tense music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[phone ringing]
Boss?
We need to leave right now.
-Abort the mission.
-Okay, boss.
-[clapping]
-[suspenseful music playing]
Papa! You're really pushing
through with this wedding?!
I thought it was just a sham!
Are we really prioritizing this
over our problem with Lily Cruz?!
Papa, you know,
I thought you were a genius.
But you know, I'm starting to think
that your brain has been lobotomized.
[scoffs] Lobotomized? Look at me, Emilia.
Do I look like somebody
cut my head open and
cut away a part of my brain?!
Emilia, I did not stay in power this long
because I am easily fooled by people.
All our enemies… Line them up.
Diego, Camia Cruz, Lily Cruz, Jaguar,
and whoever else has gone against us,
I promise you, they will all die
after the elections.
Why?
Because we have to wait till then
so that no bad publicity will
smear Arnaldo's reputation
right before he is elected into office.
So, Ivy Aguas will fool us until then?
[chuckling] Do I really have
to spell it out for you?
Ivy Aguas is not fooling us.
We are fooling her!
We are just using Ivy Aguas
for her money and the good PR
she brings with her forthcoming
royal wedding
to your son, my grandson,
and yada, yada, yada!
And after all of that,
when we have sucked Ivy Aguas
bone-dry of her money,
and her good public image, then maybe,
she can be my present to you,
and you can do whatever you want with her.
Now, is that a clear enough
explanation for you?
Or do I have to make
a PowerPoint presentation?
No need, Papa. I get it.
[scoffs]
You look surprised.
You know, your old man here…
For your information,
I am technology savvy.
If only politics didn't steal me away,
I could have been…
like Bill Gates and Steve Jobs
rolled into one.
But the call to serve
the people got to me first.
-[laughs]
-For public service!
Yes!
I'm too good.
Okay. Oops!
What? Can I come in?
No.
You seem to have enjoyed
my last treat for you too much.
I just gave you a massage, you know.
Hon, you can wait, right?
Just one more week.
Okay. Fine.
I'll see you tomorrow, my future wife.
I'll see you tomorrow, my future husband.
I just really hope that…
no one gets in the way
of our wedding again.
If you're talking about my mother,
Grandpa's handling her now.
Okay.
So, stop worrying.
I will never let anyone…
[kisses]
…stop our wedding.
[whispers] No one.
[giggles]
Hon…
One week…
-[sighs]
-…and I'm all yours.
You can do everything after that.
See you tomorrow.
One week.
-Yes.
-Can't wait.
[water running]
[turns off tap]
[exhales]
I'm glad you're here.
Now, we can talk.
[ominous music playing]
[clicks tongue] See…
This… Ivy,
whom you love so much,
will soon…
be…
[whispers] …mine.
[in normal voice] Mine. Not yours. Mine.
This woman that challenged you,
stimulated every fiber of your being,
will soon…
be…
[whispers] …mine.
[in normal voice] Not yours. Mine.
And I can't wait.
[in growly voice] I can't wait.
[whispers] I can't wait.
[in normal voice] I've been
waiting for the longest time.
And soon, she'll be mine.
Ivy Aguas.
[tense music playing]
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
I'll make her happy.
I'll make her so happy.
[laughing]
[inhales sharply]
[laughs maniacally]
Can't wait.
You have such high hopes, Arnaldo.
But I'll make sure
that you will fall just as far.
You'll be punished for the things you did
very, very soon.
[soft music playing]
Anna…
Yes?
I just want to thank you.
What for?
For helping out.
For supporting us.
I'd also like to apologize
if I didn't immediately
acknowledge your efforts
because I was too busy
worrying about my own daughter.
But I want you to know that
I'm really grateful to you,
and that I'm really happy
you're here with me.
Me too, Auntie Camia.
Now that Nanny Carlotta
isn't here anymore,
and after everything that's happened,
I've come to treat you like family.
[both chuckle softly]
[chuckles]
-Let's go home?
-Yes.
[both chuckle]
I know what you're thinking, Auntie.
"Poor little loser Emilia."
I'm such a loser, Aunt Claire.
I'm going to be drinking my failures away.
[chuckles]
I didn't say that, Emilia.
Besides, I thought you and your father
already had a plan for Ivy Aguas.
So, what is this pity party for?
Auntie…
I will no longer be
the queen of this house.
As it is, look at the way
our men treat me now.
I'm an afterthought.
And by the time Ivy Aguas joins us,
I'll just be a black hole
in the Ardiente solar system.
Of course not. You're the star.
From your perspective, Auntie, yes, I am.
But the truth is…
[scoffs] …I'm done.
I'm so over, Aunt Claire.
No. You still have time
to stop the wedding.
[sinister music playing]
Why don't you see how far
Ivy Aguas is willing to go
to become part of this family?
Thank you, my friend.
I trust that your men will stop at nothing
until that bastard is arrested.
Thank you.
[exhales]
[uneasy piano music playing]
[pills rattle]
I can't die.
[suspenseful music playing]
Not until I kill that bastard Jaguar.
I am Julio Ardiente!
And I will decide when I will die!
Boss.
Open it.
[tense music playing]
[Jepoy] What's this for?
[man 2] If you hadn't warned our boss,
we would've gotten into bigger trouble.
This money is nothing,
compared to his freedom.
That was nothing, boss.
This is too much.
Just take it already.
I think you forget just how much
money and weapons we have.
This is practically spare change.
Boss Jaguar, your group is the only one
that can fight the Ardientes.
You can't afford to waste
your money and resources.
[tense music playing]
-[door closes]
-[tense music playing]
Jepoy.
Jepoy, what's that?
Anna.
Look at this.
[tense music playing]
Jepoy, where did you get all that?
It doesn't matter.
Just help me keep these safe.
They're important to my plans.
No, Jepoy, no.
I don't need the money or weapons.
Ivy's not going to like this.
You'll just fight again!
We're practically siblings now.
Let's not ruin that--
I know that, Anna!
Anna, remember that you're in Ardiente.
You won't last here
if you put your feelings first.
You have to know the rules of the game.
You have to protect yourself at all times.
[tense music playing]
Anna…
We aren't kids anymore.
I'll push through with my plans,
even if Ivy's against them.
Just what are you going to do, Jepoy?
I'm going to finish off Arnaldo.
[suspenseful music playing]
It's time.
-[music fades]
-[birds chirping]
Ram, can you tighten it more?
How about this, madam?
Tighter.
This tight?
Come on, tighten it all the way.
But, madam, the wedding is in a week.
Do it, Ram. Tighten it all the way.
I'll magic my way into it
on the wedding day.
-Trust me.
-Yes, madam.
Is everything okay?
Yes, Ivy, and from the looks of it,
your wedding is going to be
the most fabulous wedding
of the year here in Ardiente.
I think it'll even be better
than my wedding.
Of course, Emilia. I made sure of it.
I even invited Ardiente TV
to come and cover
the wedding preparations.
And the reporters?
They're calling this "the royal
wedding of the century."
Wow, the century?
Hmm… So, we'll be live later?
Yes. Live on air. Isn't it perfect?
Perfect! [chuckles]
Ram, I'm going back.
Make my gown fabulous.
-Yes, madam.
-Give it a long train.
-[Ram] That we'll do.
-[Emilia] All right.
[chuckles]
[quietly] Perfect.
-Hello, friends!
-[upbeat music playing]
Welcome back to Ivy and Arnaldo:
The Royal Wedding.
We'll show you
the latest developments and preparations
for the coming wedding of the century.
And here she is.
Miss Ivy!
-Hi, Phomella. Hello.
-Hello. Hello, Miss Ivy.
How are you?
Well, I'm happy.
-[Phomella] One week to go.
-[Ivy] Yes.
In one week, you're going to be
Mrs. Ivy Ardiente-Torillo.
How does it feel?
[tense music playing]
Auntie, is it ready?
Yes, Emilia.
[breathes deeply]
That's great.
I'm happy. I feel happy.
This is the most exciting time
in a woman's life,
which is why I'm enjoying it.
I want to thank the viewers at home,
and the people of Poblacion Ardiente.
Thank you for supporting
the love Arnaldo and I share.
Thank you so much.
Miss Ivy, thank you as well
for inviting us to interview you
and to cover the wedding preparations.
[Ivy] Of course, Phomella.
We want all of Ardiente
to be updated on what's
happening with our wedding.
And we are very, very excited.
[Phomella] Thank you.
Thank you, Miss Ivy Aguas.
Or, wait, should I say, the soon-to-be
Mrs. Ivy Ardiente-Torillo.
-[Ivy] That's so nice to hear.
-[Phomella] Thank you.
[Jepoy] Now that I have money and weapons,
I will stop your wedding
with bullets, Arnaldo.
[Emilia] I prepared
a prenuptial agreement.
Should you and Arnaldo decide to separate,
one hundred percent of your assets
will go to Arnaldo.
[Claire] You better do it
successfully, Emilia.
Not only will Ivy hit you again,
but Arnaldo and Julio might even kill you.
[Julio] I'm throwing you a stag party
on the same day as Ivy's bridal shower.
[Emilia] Just look at what
I prepared for you.
We're going to have fun tonight.
[Ivy] Is this part of your plan, Emilia?
Okay, let's have fun.
I can keep up with any of your games.
[muffled exclaim]
[Emilia] How the hell did you get that?!
I am Ivy Aguas, remember?
[theme music playing]